lqdmarkets.com 2015-03-17

# Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy governs the collection and use of personal information relating to potential and existing customers of LQD Markets (UK) LTD by the company. Personal information is only collected in order to provide LQD Markets (UK) LTD clients with outstanding service and to better understand client requirements.

LQD Markets (UK) Ltd is committed to abiding by this Privacy Policy, as well as the requirements of applicable laws, in the operation of its business. Please read this policy carefully as it explains the kinds of personal information we collect about you and how it is handled.

By your continued use of our services (including our website), you consent to the collection and use of your personal information for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy.

####  COLLECTION/ USAGE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

We collect personal information about you which we require to respond to your enquiries for payment processing and for the provision of services to you and this information remains highly confidential. We also process your personal information where we are required to do so by law, and for the exercise or defense of legal claims. From time to time, we may contact you to tell you about our services in accordance with your contact preferences, always with your consent to do so. Personal information collected from you may include your name, payment processing information, postal address, email address, landline or mobile telephone number, as well as other non sensitive personal information. If you use our web sites, we may also collect information about you or your computer when you browse to allow you to use the services available.  
.

####  WEBSITE & USE OF COOKIES

If you are using our web sites, we will use your personal information to help you to log in to your account and into restricted areas of our web sites and to permit future use of the web sites. We may use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, or to administer our web sites. We may conduct analyses of user traffic to measure the use of our sites and to improve the content of our web sites and our services. These analyses will be performed through the use of IP addresses and cookies. We may also use cookies to enable the signing in process after you have registered with us and to provide you with more tailored information when you return to our web sites. A cookie is a piece of information that is stored on your computer’s hard drive by your web browser. Most browsers accept cookies automatically, but usually you can alter the settings of your browser to prevent automatic acceptance. If you reject the use of cookies please note that the efficient operation of our web site may be affected.

####  THIRD PARTY

We will only disclose personal information about you internally and to third parties for processing purposes associated with payment processing, the supply of services, for web site administration, or elsewhere when you have consented to such disclosures, or where such disclosures are required or permitted by law. These third parties we contractually bound only to use personal information to perform the services that we hire them to provide.

####  DATA TRANSFER

Third party data processors, advertisers, exhibitors and other such business relationships outside of the EEA, are required to take adequate technical and organisational safeguards to protect personal information. We also take measures to ensure that personal information transferred by us outside of the EEA is adequately protected.

####  SECURITY OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

We use administrative, technical, and physical measures to safeguard personal information against loss, theft and unauthorised use, access or modifications. Certain areas of our web sites may be password protected. If you are a user of our web sites and have a password, you can help to preserve your privacy by ensuring that you do not share your password with anyone else.

We take steps to regularly validate the personal information we hold to ensure that the information is accurate and, where necessary, up to date. Information that is no longer required for any valid business purpose, and that we are not required to keep pursuant to any applicable law, will be routinely destroyed by secure means.

####  CHANGES TO PRIVACY POLICY

We reserve the right to add to or amend this privacy policy at our sole discretion, without prior notice to you. Please review our privacy policy on a regular basis to make sure you have read the latest version and you understand what we do with your personal information. Your continued use of our services or our web sites following the posting of changes to these terms means that you consent to those changes.

This privacy policy is effective as of 01.11.2012
